[ominous music playing]
[siren wailing]
[indistinct chatter]
I don't remember you.
-Does it matter?
-No.
Smart decision, Hoffman.
I look at you,
and you seem almost normal.
Arrogant but normal.
I thought I'd get to see
what evil really looked like...
but you just look like
everyone else.
Is that it? Can I go now?
This is everything
that I took from you.
My representatives
will keep one safety copy.
If your thugs
follow me out of here,
if anything happens to me,
that copy
goes to law enforcement--
I know how this works.
I need to take a picture.
Of us.
[McVie] Two old buddies.
[shutter clicks]
Hope you frame it.
Good luck with your new life,
Mr. Hoffman.
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues]
Thanks for waiting.
Uptown, please.
I'll tell you where in a minute.
[suspenseful music continues]
[beeping]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[woman speaking indistinctly
over PA]
[bell rings]
[tapping]
[door buzzes]
[music fades out]
[elevator bell dings]
[indistinct chatter nearby]
[soft dramatic music playing]
[line ringing]
[automated voice] Special
answering service, inbox 482.
One new message.
[McVie on message]
We have the report back.
You've been paid
for your services.
As long as Hoffman
sticks to his side of the deal,
we're done.
And by the way,
a message from my boss.
You're parasitic scum.
[voice mail beeps]
[squeaking]
[train rumbling]
[beeping]
[digital lock beeps]
-[voice mail beeps]
-Hoffman here.
He showed last night.
I handed over the documents
and took the train
to Poughkeepsie as instructed.
I hope the safety copy
is enough
to keep Optimo off my back
and yours.
I sent the other half
of the money
to the address you provided.
I wasn't expecting
so much myself.
I thought that would go
for your fee. Thank you.
[train rumbling in distance]
Are they gonna play fair?
[voice mail beeps]
[beeping]
[clicks]
[train horn blares]
[flames crackling]
[somber music playing]
[woman] Ms. Grant?
Hi. I'm Julie.
-Hi.
-Mr. Morel will see you now.
Thank you.
[clears throat]
I was in a team,
uh, developing
a new wheat strain
resistant to insect predation
through precision breeding.
It's... It's like
genetic modification,
only it's using
natural processes,
so it's not subject
to the same tight regulation.
Anyway.
We were making progress,
but we were noticing possible
human food-chain issues.
Um, and then I was CC'ed
on an e-mail chain
where one of the attachments
was a food safety assessment
showing significant
side effects.
When I raised this issue
with senior management,
um, they told me that
I'd seen the data out of context
and not to worry.
But then, um,
soon, I was transferred
to another department
here in Manhattan.
Office work, data assessment.
Um, and then, two months later,
I was dismissed
on a minor time card violation,
and now I'm being subjected
to escalating harassment.
Uh...
I'm sorry to hear that,
Ms. Grant.
Why do you think
this is happening?
I felt, um...
Well, I felt I had a duty
to take a copy
of the food safety assessment
as evidence.
You stole documents
from your former employers?
Is that... Is that stealing?
May I ask why you decided
to discuss this issue
with our firm?
I followed a recommendation.
May I ask from whom?
A friend. It wouldn't be
appropriate to say who.
Ms. Grant, I commend you
on your intentions here,
but we're no longer looking
for this type of business.
Uh, there are a number
of highly regarded
whistleblower
support organizations
much better prepared--
No. It's not
whistleblowing support I need.
It's the opposite.
I just want
to give everything back
and promise to keep my mouth
shut and get on with my life.
[whimpers softly]
Please. Please.
Is there anyone who can help me?
[somber music playing]
Well, as I said, there are
official channels, but, uh...
Look, um...
There are unofficial ones
we've referred people to
in the past.
Just take this number,
and maybe they can help you.
[sniffles]
-Who is he?
-I've never met him,
or her or they.
That's kind of the point.
It's a messaging service.
They call you back...
or they don't.
Just be honest
about your situation.
[somber music continues]
-[alarm beeping]
-[music fades out]
[train horn blaring in distance]
[car horn honks]
You are all set.
The lobby's attended
24 hours a day.
Call if you need anything.
Thanks for doing this
on short notice.
That's what we do.
Enjoy your stay.
[door closes]
[suspenseful music playing]
Hey, I'm Wash,
and I'm an alcoholic.
-Hi, Wash.
Um...
I've been sober nine years,
nine months.
And...
It's been even more
of a struggle recently
because there's
why I drank in the first place,
and then there's me
doing what I do.
'Cause I'm proud
of serving on the force.
And I stay on the up and up.
Pretty much. [chuckles]
But, um...
What I see on the daily,
amongst my fellow officers...
I... I... I don't know.
[indistinct chatter
and laughter nearby]
[automated voice]
Two new messages.
[on message]
Hoffman here. All right.
[voice mail beeps]
[on message]
My name is Sarah Grant.
Um, I was a scientist
working at a biotech company,
Cybo Sementis.
I... I'm in possession
of materials
which are evidence
of an unlawful cover-up.
I was gonna go public,
but I changed my mind.
I don't know how this works,
but I'll do
whatever is necessary.
My number is 693-824-4011.
[voice mail beeps]
[pensive music playing]
[keyboard keys clacking]
♪ If you felt alive ♪
♪ I couldn't tell ♪
♪ It's coming to an end ♪
♪ The world is now ♪
We are delighted
to be the recipients
of the Lansing Award.
This research has the potential
to revolutionize grain yields,
particularly in developing
countries, where they need it,
lowering reliance
on pesticides.
And with this grant,
we really hope
to make a difference.
♪ Far from this place ♪
♪ A brand-new way... ♪
[cellphone ringing]
[operator] Hello. This is
the Tri-State Relay Service.
-Yes. Hello.
-A person is calling
through relay service. Have you
received a relay call before?
-I don't think so.
-The person who has called you
is likely to be deaf
or hard of hearing.
The caller will type
their conversation,
and I'll read it to you.
When it's your turn,
I'll type everything you say.
Speak directly to the caller
and say, "Go ahead,"
when you're ready
for a response.
No calls are recorded,
and everything you say
is confidential.
One moment
for your call to begin.
"You are Sarah Elizabeth Grant.
Your Social Security number
is 958-00-4493."
[teletype beeping]
"You were employed by Cybo
Sementis Research Institutes,
tax ID 99-0890590, based
in St. Louis. Is that correct?"
Yes.
If finished,
please respond with "Go ahead."
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Go ahead.
"Please explain your situation."
I was in a research group
developing a new strain
of insect-resistant wheat.
Um, a food-safety report
came back
with disturbing data
about side effects.
I told my bosses.
Next thing I knew,
I'd been reassigned
and later dismissed.
Production of the new strain
has gone ahead,
but these findings
have been suppressed.
Um, but I was able to get a copy
of that food safety report
out of the building.
Go ahead.
"You mention side effects."
In a small number of cases,
there were extreme allergies,
anaphylaxis.
And in longer-term cases,
diverticulitis
and cancer
well above base rate.
They project
massive worldwide sales.
Thousands of people
will be affected.
But without
the information I have,
it will be impossible
to trace it back
to the food people have eaten.
[teletype beeping]
"Would you say this document
contains clear evidence
of malfeasance?"
Compared to the fraudulent
version of their report, yes.
Go ahead.
"Did they offer you
a cash settlement
in exchange for your silence?"
Um, initially, yes,
but I wasn't interested.
I wanted to do the right thing.
But then
the intimidation started.
[teletype beeping]
Last night,
they set my car on fire.
Go ahead.
"Are the police involved?"
They towed the car away
as evidence,
but I haven't involved them.
-Go ahead.
-"Don't.
Was this at 200 Chambers Street
in Tribeca?"
Yes.
But I've moved now
because of the threats.
Go ahead.
[keyboard keys clacking]
"Buy a prepaid cellphone,
keep it switched off
till you get to a public place,
then leave a message
with your new number,
new address,
and any further details."
There's a van parked out front.
I think they're watching me.
Go ahead.
"They may be tapping this call.
In the future,
only use your new phone."
[disconnect sound]
Your caller has hung up.
Thank you for using
the Tri-State Relay Service.
Have a wonderful night.
[Sarah on recording]
There's a van parked out front.
I think they're watching me.
Go ahead.
Okay. 339 East Avenue,
Yonkers, New York.
[operator on recording]
"Only use your new phone."
Night shift. Who's coming?
[soft tense music playing]
The Americans with Disabilities
Act of 1990, Section 225,
prohibits relay operators
from disclosing the content
of any relayed conversation
and from keeping records
of the content
of any such conversation
beyond the duration of the call.
Okay. Okay. I don't want to go
and get a warrant. Do you?
-No.
-Where'd you say you're from?
-Treasury Department.
-Misappropriations.
Okay. Even with a warrant,
there'd be nothing to search.
We don't keep
records of our logs,
where they're coming from,
or where they're going to.
Mm.
This is Sarah Grant.
Um, my new number
is 718-493-7071.
1500 Washington Street,
apartment 2Q, uh, 10006.
[clears throat] The company is
on the verge of being acquired
based on an estimated value
of $3.2 billion,
which will be confirmed
at an SEC filing next week.
If the information I had
went public,
it would break that deal.
They are highly incentivized
to prevent that,
which is why I'm scared.
[dramatic music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[siren whooping]
[car horn honks]
[car horns honking]
[door buzzes]
[cellphone rings]
-Hello.
-A person is calling you
through Relay Service. Have you
received a relay call before?
Yes. Go ahead.
"After reviewing your
situation, here's the deal.
We can help you
return the documents
whilst maintaining leverage
to protect you.
We require
a $50,000 deposit up front.
This will be returned to you
from money we recover
during the negotiation process.
Can you afford this?"
Yes. Go ahead.
"Over the next few days,
you will receive
some strange requests
designed to show us
what we're up against.
Please follow all instructions
no matter how odd.
In the future,
we will use a passcode
before each conversation.
We will say, 'Credit or debit?'
You will say, 'Check.'
-Understood?"
-Understood.
[suspenseful music playing]
[vehicle backup alarm beeping]
[suspenseful music continues]
[buzzing]
Who is it?
[man] Package for you.
[suspenseful music continues]
Thanks.
[cellphone ringing]
-Hello.
-Tri-State Relay Service.
Have you received
a relay call before?
Yes. Go ahead.
Credit or debit?
Check. Go ahead.
"Tomorrow morning,
take the 10:05 flight
from Newark to Pittsburgh,
then the 11:50 to Atlanta.
Do not take this phone with you.
Take the packages
with our deposit
and the report and the
red-marked phone you were sent.
Do not turn it on until you are
at your gate in Pittsburgh."
Your caller has hung up.
Operator, I forgot something.
Can I call back?
The caller has placed
a no-callback request
on this line. Sorry, ma'am.
-[indistinct chatter]
-[plane passing overhead]
[dramatic music playing]
[woman] Next.
[man speaking indistinctly
over PA]
-Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
Hello.
[barcode scanner beeps]
[woman over PA] This is
a preboarding announcement
for Flight 8917 to Atlanta.
We are expecting
a full flight today,
so if you'd like
to gate-check your bag,
please see us at the desk.
[dramatic music continues]
[cellphone beeps]
Hello.
I found this bag
up by Gate B17.
Let me guess. Near the bathroom?
-Yeah. How did you know?
-Happens all the time.
It says "Sarah Grant" on it.
-Okay. I'll take it from here.
-Okay. Good luck.
[music fades out]
[cellphone ringing]
Hello?
Credit or--
Check.
Go ahead.
"Where are you now?"
At the gate.
Um, we're about to board.
Um, what should I do? Go ahead.
"Do you have the packages?"
-Yes. Go ahead.
-"Good."
[woman over PA]
Passenger Sarah Grant,
please come
to the lost-property counter.
Passenger Sarah Grant.
Lost-property counter.
I'm gonna check it out.
[operator]
"Ignore everything else
and await instructions."
[woman over PA]
Passenger Sarah Grant,
please come
to the lost-property counter.
"Go to the post office
in concourse D
and mail both packages.
We will call you back."
Sir, may I help you
with something?
[woman over PA]
Passenger Sarah Grant,
please report to Gate A29.
I'm never flying
your airline again.
[dramatic music playing]
-Where is she?
-No-show.
They keep calling her name.
She didn't show up.
Wanna do another lap?
If they're following her,
they gotta be in here somewhere.
[woman over PA]
Final call for Grant,
for Flight 8317 to Atlanta.
Passenger Sarah Grant.
Final call for Atlanta.
[sighs]
They're not following her.
What do you mean?
We're made.
[dramatic music continues]
[sighs]
-Where are you?
-[Rosetti] You won't believe it,
but she's at the post office.
Okay.
And this one is
Norman, Oklahoma, 73019.
Anything liquid,
fragile, hazardous?
No.
So, your tracking numbers
are right here.
And if you wanna fill out
a survey, it's right there.
-Okay.
-Okay?
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
So, the tracking number
is 840-59-70-0233803.
[dramatic music continues]
[music fades out]
Okay. So, what can we learn?
Hm? 'Cause
the airport security thing,
it was smart, it was tight.
Why send us
all the way to Pittsburgh?
Since 2001, the TSA has closed
over 113 airport branches
of the United States
Post Office.
The only one remaining
inside security
is Pittsburgh.
All right. So, there's
two P.O. Box addresses.
Split us up and keep us running.
Looks like it's fucking working.
Yep. Yep.
You know what I think?
I think I like this one.
-Hoorah.
-[all chuckle]
[Lee] They're smarter
than we thought.
[chuckles]
Hey, do you have those
tracking numbers for me?
-There you go.
-Let's see where we're going.
Check. Go ahead.
"Good job. Please confirm that
you've sent all the documents
-and have no further copies."
-I confirm.
Were... Were they there today
at the airport? Go ahead.
"Yes."
So, you were, too? Go ahead.
[keyboard keys clacking]
"Do not contact them yourself.
Do not respond
if they contact you.
They may try to scare you, and
they may try to make a deal.
But this is the only deal.
Once the packages arrive,
we will make them an offer.
You're going to meet them once
to make the return yourself."
Do I have to? Go ahead.
"By then, you will have
all the leverage you need."
And you'll be there? Go ahead.
[keyboard keys clacking]
"You will never meet us.
We are not bodyguards.
We are intermediaries.
We will broker a deal to return
the original documents
and retain one safety copy
to make sure Cybo Sementis
sticks to that deal.
Follow our instructions,
and you will be protected.
But if you don't,
you will put yourself in danger
and we will walk away."
I understand. Go ahead.
"Your old phone
will be compromised.
Put it in a pan of salt water.
Use this one now."
Your caller has hung up.
Thank you for using
the Tri-State Relay Service.
Have a wonderful night.
[call disconnects]
[ASG's "Survive Sunrise"
playing]
♪ Strike for your eyes ♪
♪ When I'm seeking ♪
♪ A heart in the sky ♪
♪ Worth believing ♪
♪ When I feel ♪
♪ Like suffering some... ♪
-[line ringing]
-[music volume turns down]
Hey. Yeah.
I got a camera in position.
But I don't got nothing.
What about you?
How's Michigan treating you?
[Rosetti] I'm guessing better
than Bumfuck, Oklahoma.
-[Ryan chuckles] Damn.
-[Rosetti] It's really pretty.
♪ Like those suffering some ♪
-Hi.
-Hi. I wanna pick up a package
for my friend Archie.
He's got box 521.
I have the tracking number,
but I forgot the key.
Would you be able
just to grab it for me?
Well, I'm afraid, ma'am,
that regulations
do not permit me
to open mailboxes
for our clients.
-Oh, no. Really?
-Sorry.
It's my fault. Should've
remembered the darn key.
-Yeah.
-[sighs]
Just... My dog is really sick.
-Oh.
-Yeah. My head is a mess.
I... I'm sorry.
-Well, that's a shame, ma'am.
-Yeah.
She's just a... tired old girl.
-Aw.
-Won't be too much longer now.
[Rosetti sighs]
I don't suppose
you'd be able to just check
to see if the package
has arrived?
Oh. Um...
Uh, okay.
-Thank you.
-You wait here.
[sighs]
I'm sorry, ma'am.
There's nothing there.
Well, it was sent Priority Mail.
It should have already arrived.
I'm sorry.
Huh. Okay.
Not a good day.
Did your friend recently move,
by any chance?
If they did, there would be
a forwarding address on file,
and if it was rerouted,
well, that could explain
the delay.
Yes. Mail forwarding.
Oh, my gosh.
That makes total sense.
He just moved here, actually.
Can you tell me something?
Will the new destination show up
on that old tracking number?
Now, there's the thing.
Tracking does not always
carry over to forwarding
because they're
different services.
Huh.
[Bush Tetras' "Too Many Creeps"
playing]
♪ I just don't wanna go ♪
♪ Out in the streets no more ♪
♪ Because these people
They give me ♪
♪ They give me the creeps ♪
♪ Anymore ♪
♪ Too many creeps ♪
♪ I don't wanna ♪
♪ It's the worst ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
[operator] "This is a message
for Mr. Franklin.
We've been given a copy
of a food safety assessment
of Cybo Sementis's
Fertile Crescent wheat program
by Sarah Grant,
a former employee of yours,
who has engaged our services.
It is 311 pages long
and contains two appendices.
In exchange for
your unconditional agreement
to leave her alone,
our client would like
to return this document
and agree
never to mention it again."
[dramatic music playing]
[operator] "Our client would
like to return this document
and agree
never to mention it again.
All communication with her
must come through us.
Leave a message
on 646-167-1573.
We will contact you
with further instructions."
Callback number is the same.
Goes to the messaging service.
Check out the answer service HQ.
I tried that. Client protection
is super tight.
[cellphone ringing nearby]
[cellphone continues ringing]
-Hello?
-[operator] A person is calling
from the
Tri-State Relay Service.
Have you received
a relay call before?
"You've been harassing
our client, Sarah Grant.
Please stop."
She violated her NDA,
and she's holding on
to stolen research,
so no can do. Go ahead.
"And now she's given it to us.
In case you're doubting this,
page nine starts with:
'The enhancement
of clerodane diterpenes
in Fertile Crescent
sample 7...'"
All right. I understand.
Go ahead.
"We've left word at the office
of Cybo Sementis's CEO,
Mr. Franklin.
We await his response."
Mr. Franklin passed on your
message. [whispering] Track it.
And he's authorized us to speak
on his behalf. Go ahead.
"Who am I speaking to,
and what is your position?"
Well, my name is Steve Dawson.
Don't look it up. It's not real.
And my team is tasked
with returning the documents.
Go ahead.
"We wish to return them
as soon as possible,
but in order
to protect our client,
we are ready
to send them simultaneously
to all appropriate
law-enforcement agencies
as well as every major
media outlet
if you don't fully cooperate...
-[mouthing]
-...with our requests."
We'll do our best to cooperate.
Go ahead.
"There will be no more threats
to our client, no surveillance,
including phone taps.
Once we are satisfied
with our client's security,
we'll return the original.
We will keep a single
secure copy as insurance
for our client's protection."
How do we know to trust you?
You could be anyone. Go ahead.
"You will be our client, too.
You will be required
to pay a fee.
We work for both parties
to ensure
that the job is done
with no loose ends.
It is in all our interests
for it to run smoothly."
That's very kind of you.
How much is the fee?
Go ahead.
-"Half a million dollars cash."
-That's a lot of money.
How do we trust your client's
intentions? Go ahead.
"You were tapping
our client's first calls.
You know as much about
their intentions as we do."
I'm gonna have to run it
internally. Go ahead.
"You have until
end of day tomorrow
to confirm your acceptance."
Yeah, understood. Go ahead.
"Now get a new parking spot
and stay away from our client."
Your caller has hung up.
Thank you for using
Tri-State Relay Service.
Have a wonderful--
[disconnect tone]
[suspenseful music playing]
Let's go.
[engine starts]
Credit or debit?
[Sarah] Check.
The surveillance van is gone.
Thank you.
[beeping]
"Good. Now we wait
for a few days.
You will need to be patient
and stay calm.
Once they fulfill
their end of the deal,
we'll arrange
to return the documents
before the SEC deadline
next week.
After that, you will need
to relocate for a while.
Ideally, somewhere
in this country you can reach
by public transportation
so they can't track you.
It is for your protection
and shouldn't be permanent."
I understand.
Go ahead.
Hey, um, the weather
is getting better.
Um, is it okay if I spend
some time outside? Go ahead.
"They should leave you alone.
If you see anything
that worries you, let us know."
How?
You're not that easy
to get ahold of. Go ahead.
"After 6 p.m. each day,
leave a message
at the number you have.
Just one word.
If something is wrong,
say, 'Weather.'
If everything's okay,
say, 'Alright.'"
"All right" is two words,
not one. Go ahead.
[teletype beeping]
[keyboard keys clacking]
"Ever listen to The Who?
First album.
First track on the B side."
-[keyboard keys clacking]
-[teletype disconnecting]
Your caller has hung up.
Thank you for--
[disconnect tone]
[siren wailing in distance]
I see you at meetings,
but I've never seen you share.
How long you sober?
Nineteen months.
What step you on?
I've been kicking around
step four.
-Mm-hmm.
-For a minute, actually.
-Moral inventory?
-Yeah.
Resentments?
Yeah. I got a lot of those.
[chuckles] You working?
What kind of gig?
Mostly delivery.
Parcels, food, stuff like that.
I got a little something
on the side, too.
Legal?
[chuckles]
You don't wanna tell me?
Dangerous?
We're addicts, Jon.
We do addicty things.
And we just gotta be
aware of them and pull back
so we don't replace
one addiction with a new one.
What if what you're doing
is important
and somebody has to do it?
Well, you have to decide
how important.
Listen, however you're managing,
you just don't need to do it
all on your own.
The fact is...
you can't.
[beeping]
They've agreed to your terms.
How do we transfer the money?
What do you want us to do next?
"Send unmarked cash
to P.O. Box 897,
Landers, California, 92285,
overnight priority.
When it has been
safely received,
we will issue
further instructions.
Any delay
and the document goes public."
Your caller has hung up.
Thank you for using
the Tri-State Relay Service.
And have a wonderful day.
He's brazen.
Okay. Oh.
[Ryan] How long do the batteries
in those things last?
[Lee] Four or five days.
Should be enough.
-[Ryan] Right?
-[Dawson] Fuck you, pal.
-Box it up.
-Glad I don't have to pay it.
[Lee] The tracker is activated.
That's cool.
[The Heliocentrics'
"Made Of The Sun" playing]
♪ Every piece of the puzzle ♪
♪ Falls into one ♪
♪ I'm made of the flesh ♪
♪ I'm made of the sun ♪
♪ Sketchbook falls wide open ♪
♪ Just be like a child ♪
♪ How can we be different ♪
♪ Born to be wild ♪
♪ My seed of insight
Seems so slow to grow ♪
♪ Coming to fruit now
Aware, I know ♪
♪ I felt your ♪
♪ I felt your presence
Right from the start ♪
♪ No more as strangers ♪
♪ Will we ever part ♪
♪ Oh, and last of the hope ♪
♪ Born from despair ♪
♪ End of the road ♪
♪ But I pray, I pray ♪
♪ I pray ♪
♪ Teary-eyed on the floor ♪
♪ I found inspiration ♪
♪ What hurt me the most ♪
♪ Brought incarnation ♪
[automated voice]
Special answering service.
Inbox 482. One new message.
[Dawson]
The package has been sent.
Tracking number 4739-27721.
The filing deadline's less
than a week away,
so ball's in your court.
[Hoffman on message] All right.
[voice mail beeps]
[Sarah on message]
All... right.
[chuckles]
[Dabrye's "Fightscene" playing]
♪ Fight scene ♪
♪ Ride on 'em, buckle up
Hands up, knuckle up ♪
♪ Fight scene, fight scene ♪
♪ Ride on 'em, buckle up
Hands up, knuckle up ♪
♪ Fight scene, fight scene ♪
[communicating in sign language]
[song stops]
You know what it is, man.
Work, work.
Yeah. Uh, I need an ID.
Minnesota? Yeah. That's fine.
Getting harder, huh?
Three days? That's cool, man.
Oh, price--
Oh, motherfucker. Okay.
What?
Bro, come on, man.
You always bullshitting me, bro.
Yo, you know me.
What is it?
Or what?
You want four?
[Agnes Obel's
"Close Watch" playing]
♪ Never win and never lose ♪
♪ There's nothing left
To choose ♪
♪ Between right and wrong ♪
♪ Nothing lost
And nothing gained ♪
♪ Still things
Ain't quite the same ♪
♪ Between you and me ♪
♪ I keep a close watch
On this heart of mine ♪
♪ I keep a close watch on-- ♪
[song stops]
[automated voice] ...482.
One new message.
[voice mail beeps]
[on message] This is Hoffman.
Optimo Pharmaceutical's
history of fraud is incredible.
They just pay the fines
and keep doing the same thing.
How many people have died
because of their lies?
Lies that I was a part of.
I missed my niece's baptism.
I wonder what else I'm missing.
[voice mail beeps]
[Sarah on message] All... right.
All is right with the world.
Joke, right? [chuckles]
I wonder
what your life is like.
[scoffs] I wonder
if you even listen this far in.
[liquid pouring]
Are you lonely?
[Sarah sips]
-[clicking]
-♪ I'm in the phone booth
♪ It's the one
Across the hall ♪
♪ If you don't answer
I'll ring it off the wall ♪
♪ I know she's there
But I just had to call ♪
♪ Don't leave me hanging
On the telephone ♪
[voice mail beeps]
[train rumbling]
[keyboard keys clacking]
[poignant music playing]
[automated voice]
Inbox 482. No new messages.
[voice mail beeps]
[poignant music continues]
[engine starts]
[cellphone ringing]
Yes.
[Jon] This is
Tri-State Relay Service.
Have you received
a relay call before?
Yes. Check.
Sorry I didn't call.
Is something wrong? Go ahead.
I just wanted to see
if you were okay.
Yeah. I'm fine. What about you?
Are you okay? Go ahead.
I'm fine.
I listened to your message.
Interesting musical choice.
Oh, God.
You listened to the end.
Sorry. Go ahead.
How did you know there was
an original to that song?
Google.
I use modern technology.
Feels like you don't.
So, what else do you listen to
aside from The Who? Go ahead.
-Who said I listened to them?
-Oh, come on.
I've got time on my hands.
I can listen to anything
you can recommend. Go ahead.
I recommend we keep
communication to a minimum.
Well, you stuck around to listen
to all of my last message.
So, are you?
Go ahead.
Am I what?
Lonely.
Go ahead.
It's strange talking to someone
who knows so much about you
when you know so little
about them.
May I ask you a question?
Go ahead.
It depends what it is.
Has it ever gone wrong?
Go ahead.
Sometimes people run.
Sometimes we have to walk away.
The instructions,
not everybody listens.
I'll try hard to behave myself.
Good night.
[disconnect tone]
That was a new number. Run it.
Nice. It's already off.
-[clerk] Okay, you're all set.
-Thank you.
-Hi.
I have a mailbox in California.
That's where I normally live.
But I'm going away to Europe
for a month on business.
I know. Poor me.
Um, could I please have all
my mail forwarded to my cousin
-who lives in Poughkeepsie?
-Yes. That's possible.
And she's actually moving.
So, what do I do?
-Send it to General Delivery?
-Yep. You got it.
She'll need an ID
to pick anything up.
All right. Cool.
Let's do that. Thank you.
So, it'll be coming
from Landers, California.
And the name of the person
it's going to?
Sarah with an "H." Grant.
Mm-hmm.
[indistinct chatter]
[traffic humming]
[siren wailing nearby]
-[voice mail beeps]
-[on message] This is Dawson.
According to the USPS,
the money's been delivered.
The SEC filing
is in three days,
so we're expecting
handover arrangements
as soon as possible.
But we have a problem.
You told Mr. Franklin
you had a 311-page document.
But the full report
is 327 pages
with a 16-page
third appendix.
We need all the pages returned.
Otherwise, why did we pay
half a million dollars?
Tick-tock, motherfucker.
[beeping]
[operator]
"You told us that you had sent
all the relevant documents."
I did.
-Go ahead.
-"What about Appendix C?
It's missing."
There was no info there.
It was all just small print.
Nothing pertaining
to the research. Go ahead.
[dramatic music playing]
"Why would you leave it out?"
I just didn't think.
"Do you still have it?"
-Yes, I do. Go ahead.
-"They need it."
I will send it to you
like before. Go ahead.
"Takes too long.
You were warned.
You must follow the steps,
or we can't protect you."
Please don't leave me to do this
by myself. [cries softly]
[train horn blaring]
[tense music playing]
"There's a newsstand on the
corner of 7th and West 46th.
Put the envelope in the pages
of the bottom copy
of The Washington Post, which
is the second pile on the left.
Then leave the area."
[tense music continues]
[siren wailing nearby]
Go.
[tense music continues]
[buzzes]
-Thank you.
-[clerk] Yeah. No problem.
-How's it going?
-[clerk] It's going.
[Jon] Yeah?
[clerk] Just that?
[whistles]
[tense music continues]
[Ryan] Could I get your photo?
Doing this thing on New Yorkers
in their natural habitat.
You know what I'm saying?
[tense music continues]
Come on!
I left it in the Post, bottom
copy, left pile like you said.
"The Washington Post
is second from the left."
Second from the left.
I'm so sorry.
Everything happened so fast.
Um, I'll come back for it.
[keyboard keys clacking]
"It'll be gone by then. Did you
know you were being followed?"
[Sarah]
No. I thought they stopped that.
I'm so sorry. It's my fault.
Don't walk away.
[keyboard keys clacking]
[disconnect tone]
It's my birthday, bitch!
It's my birthday,
and I'm getting candy!
And give me some goddamn
lottery tickets, too.
Put the...
Put the candy... Fuck.
[exclaims]
[cackling]
[dramatic music playing]
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
[dramatic music continues]
Did you get it? Did you get it?
Thank you.
Hey! Hey, hey! Where is it?
Where is it?
What the fuck, man?
Where'd you put it?
[dramatic music continues]
[music fades out]
That's him right there.
-Security guard.
-[Ryan] No shit.
It's this guy right here.
I'm sitting there, I'm watching
the guy in the fucking suit.
And this bastard is right there.
Yeah, you remember him?
[cellphone ringing]
-Yeah.
-[operator] A person is calling
through
the Tri-State Relay Service.
Have you received a call
from us before?
Yes, we have.
Just give me one second, please.
Hey, yo. Hey, hey. TTY.
[Dawson grunts]
Yeah. I'm here. Go ahead.
"We've got 40 copies,
including the missing appendix,
ready to go to spread across
the mainstream
and alternative media.
You agreed to stop following
and harassing her."
She was in Times Square
with a document that contains
sensitive material.
You wouldn't know that
if you weren't following her.
Do you want us to go public?"
We apologize. We're sorry.
We made a mistake.
And we'll do exactly as you say
from now on. Go ahead.
"The handover will be
between our client
and your CEO, Franklin,
in person,
in a public place of our choice
at 7 p.m. on Thursday."
[Dawson]
Mr. Franklin is out of town.
Well, get him back.
"Ask him to return."
Oh, yeah. I'll try my best.
Thursday is the day before
the SEC filing.
That's cutting it close.
Go ahead.
"You'd better make it work."
Your caller has hung up.
Thank you for using--
[disconnect tone]
That's it. We got our guy.
That's him.
We'll get him to our friends
at a fusion center.
For facial recognition?
I don't think it's good enough.
That's the best frame
of his face we have.
[cell phone ringing]
[cell phone continues ringing]
Your call is now connected.
Are you all right? Go ahead.
Uh, are you th--
Are you there?
Hello?
"We have it. We're setting
the exchange for Thursday.
Until then,
you'll call each day once
and leave a message.
You'll say, 'All right,'
or you'll say, 'Weather.'
Nothing more.
You'll follow instructions
because this time,
we will walk away.
Do you understand?"
Yes.
-Go ahead.
-Your caller has hung up.
Thank you for using
the Tri-State Relay Service.
Have a wonderful night.
[call disconnects]
[siren wailing in distance]
[indistinct chatter]
Hey. Um, I'd like
to book a table, please.
We tracked it as far as Bell.
There's a national distribution
center there.
Then we lost it.
Will the signal come back?
[Lee]
There were no backup batteries.
[Dawson]
Where's it gonna go from there?
It could literally be anywhere.
[tense music playing]
All right.
[on message] All right.
[voice mail beeps]
[on message] It's Hoffman.
I've been checking
the obituaries of the towns
that were part of
Optimo's trials.
Healthy young people
suddenly dying.
How many more are there?
We all knew
the trials were inadequate.
They said things were safe
way before we knew enough.
You know how widely
it was distributed.
Millions of people
will have been affected,
but Optimo will deny it.
I had a chance to do something,
and I blew it.
I've got blood on my hands.
It's not your fault.
You helped me.
Thank you.
I won't bother you again.
[voice mail beeps]
I'm Jon, and I'm an alcoholic.
[all] Hi, Jon.
Growing up Muslim, you're not
supposed to drink at all.
I, uh...
So, I grew up Muslim
in New York...
post 9/11.
It was crazy.
I figured drinking
would help me to fit in
and just connect to people more.
And it did, a little.
Didn't stop me getting
my ass kicked all the time.
But when that happened,
it would help me go numb.
So, either way, it helped.
And then I got a job
on Wall Street.
It was intense.
Drinking was part of fitting in.
And it was a way of dealing
with pressure to meet
these crazy targets.
There was no way
of meeting them.
Not without bending the rules
and screwing people over.
Much as I wanted to be
a part of something,
I didn't wanna be
a part of that.
So, I started
gathering information,
and I took it to my superiors.
They took a look at it.
And nothing really happened.
The investigation was one-sided.
It all blew over.
And when it did,
people I had known a long time
turned their backs on me,
started spreading rumors
about me.
You know, questioning my sanity
and my integrity.
And I started to become,
uh, paranoid
and aggressive and drunk.
By the time they came to me
with this severance package,
it was tied to an NDA.
I was relieved.
So, I, uh...
I took the money.
I kept my mouth shut,
poured it all down my throat.
But I still carry a lot of guilt
and shame about that time.
And I keep thinking
I was a coward.
And I was weak. I was.
I got a call from someone
last night,
and he just sounded
so... lost...
and broken.
And I don't think
he's gonna make it, honestly.
I don't wanna end up like that.
Thank you, Wash.
[suspenseful music playing]
[buzzing]
[cellphone ringing]
"The original copy of the report
is waiting under your name
in General Delivery at
the main post office on 8th.
A table is booked
for Adam Franklin
at Gaia & Loki restaurant
at 7 p.m. tonight.
Take a taxi there
and make it wait.
Bring the report in the yellow
marked phone you were sent.
When he arrives,
hand him the documents,
take a picture
of the two of you,
get back in the taxi
and head uptown.
You will receive
further instructions then.
Do you understand?"
Yes, I do. Go ahead.
Your caller has hung up.
Thank you for using
the Tri-State Relay Service.
Have a wonderful day.
"Mr. Franklin
must attend in person,
and our client will need
to take a photograph with him.
She will return the original
copy of the report,
and we will keep
a single safety copy
to ensure everyone
sticks to the deal."
Your caller has hung up.
Thank you for using
the Tri-State Relay Service.
Have a wonderful--
[dramatic music playing]
[bartender] Can I get you
another club soda?
No. I'm good.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
[dramatic music continues]
[beeping]
[automated voice]
...one new message.
[Sarah on message] Weather.
I know I should have called.
You don't have to worry.
I'm okay.
They know who you are.
They said facial recognition
got a positive ID of you
in Times Square.
They told me your name.
James Keaton.
You're in big danger, James.
This is my fault.
You've got to get out of here
and stay away.
-No, no, no, no, no.
-I screwed up in Times Square,
so I'm gonna do
this handover myself.
-Fuck!
-There's a concert
of Schubert's
Piano Trios at town hall.
It's public,
like you said it should be.
-Fuck!
-They told me not to tell you,
but I needed to.
And to thank you
for looking after me.
Goodbye, James. Be safe.
[car horns honking]
Let me get a ticket.
Here you are.
-Keep the change.
-Thank you.
[detector beeps]
[classical music playing nearby]
Whoa, what is that?
It's a hearing-assisted device
for the deaf.
All right.
Well, you gotta check it.
[classical music continues]
[line ringing]
[alarm blaring]
[music stops]
[alarm continues blaring]
[audience murmuring]
[groans]
[crowd gasps]
It's me. It's me.
Credit or debit.
It's a trap. They're coming
to get you. Come on.
[dramatic music playing]
Excuse me. Excuse me.
[dramatic music continues]
-[alarm continues blaring]
-Move, move, move!
-[siren wailing]
-Put this on.
Put this on. Take this off.
Did you give it to them?
The report.
-No.
-Good.
Our threat to go public
has to feel real.
It's the only leverage you got.
Take the train to Poughkeepsie.
You're gonna pay in cash.
When you get there,
you go to the Grand Hotel.
You book under your own name,
but you misspell it, all right?
I gotta go back to the apartment
and get my stuff.
No, you don't. You can't.
How did they get
in touch with you?
They, uh...
They rang the intercom.
Did they hurt you?
-No.
-Okay, good.
When you get there, call me
and let me know you're okay.
I'm gonna call you right ba--
We're gonna contact you
with a P.O. Box number.
All right? You're gonna
have to remember it.
Will you just tell me?
I gotta protect you
while you're traveling.
You go to the main post office,
ask for an envelope.
It's got a P.O. Box key in it
and the rest
of the instructions.
Yo!
Let's go.
Here.
Grand Central. Let's go.
You're okay.
-You got the papers?
-Yeah.
From now on, it's cash only.
Use a card,
they're gonna trace you. ID.
You got a new one waiting
for you at the post office.
Stop. Please stop.
Why did you do this for me?
It's my job.
Was that all?
You know, you're exactly and not
at all what I imagined, James.
That's not my name.
They lied to you.
What is your name?
It's Ash.
Ashraf.
[scoffs]
Am I your worst client ever,
Ashraf?
[chuckles] Maybe.
Hey.
You're gonna be all right.
Come with me, Ashraf.
I can't.
Goodbye.
Keep it.
Don't look back.
[wistful music playing]
[man speaking indistinctly
over PA]
[music fades out]
[tense music playing]
[cellphone ringing]
"What was your plan?
That I was bluffing?
I'll make sure
you never find her.
She's gone and so am I."
[teletype disconnects]
Your caller has hung up.
Thank you for using
the Tri-State Relay Service.
Have a won--
[sighs]
Thank you.
[cellphone buzzes]
Sarah, you can't use this phone.
All right?
You got to get rid of it
right away.
[Dawson] Glad to finally
hear your voice.
We're getting bored of speaking
to this fucking relay service.
This little phone has been
very useful. Thank you.
I'll get her for you.
[Sarah] Don't do what they say.
They were tracking me.
Sarah, listen to me.
You gotta stay calm.
-It's my fault.
-Listen to me.
We're gonna figure this out.
-Just stay calm for me.
-Just walk away.
[Dawson] Give it here.
You're going to do what
we say now.
-You understand?
-Listen, let her go.
All right? The documents
are going out, all of them.
-You hear me?
-And then what, huh?
The idea of journalists or
their readers actually caring,
it's a cute, liberal fantasy.
Most of the media work
with us anyway,
so they won't publish
in a hurry.
And that leaves the conspiracy
theorists on social media.
Good luck with that.
Guess what. Law enforcement
is gonna be reading
more closely,
so don't fucking push me.
The envelopes are labeled
-and sealed.
-Here's the deal.
We're gonna come with you
to wherever
you keep your documents,
and you're gonna give us
all the copies of the report,
including your safety copy,
and we'll let her go unharmed.
And you, too,
if you behave yourself.
You gotta be
out your fucking mind.
I have other clients
to consider.
You really think
you have a choice?
♪ It's just a game ♪
♪ It's just... ♪
[dramatic music playing]
[chuckling]
[line ringing]
[Dawson] Yeah?
Yeah, I'll do it.
I'll take you
to all the records. I'll do it.
That's good. That's very good.
Dawn tomorrow, you come
to your client's apartment.
-[electricity crackling]
-[Ash groans]
[gasps]
[grunts]
Sarah, you okay?
I'm fine.
[groans]
Where's the documents?
You let her go, I'll tell you.
[groans]
Stop.
You want the documents,
you need us both alive.
So, why don't you let her go,
and we'll talk.
Don't really need her.
Hey! Easy.
[wails]
-Hey!
-Where are the documents?
10001 South Second Street,
Newark.
[Lee] Newark.
10001 South Second Street.
He likes you. [chuckles]
[tires screeching]
[grunts]
[groans]
[grunting]
Oh, you motherfucker!
[grunts then yells]
[car horn honking]
[both grunting]
[soft tense music playing]
[groans]
[Ash groaning]
[Dawson] Oh, you motherfucker.
[tense music continues]
Stop.
[Dawson] Good job, boss.
[panting]
[groans]
What do you want?
We want your copy of the
Optimo Pharmaceutical report.
Yeah. This is about Hoffman.
Here, here. Here.
[groans]
[Dawson] Unlock it.
Okay, come on.
Come on.
This one? Come here.
[Ash groans]
Come on.
[Ash grunts]
This? Huh? What?
You got to untie my hands
so I can reach it.
Legs, too. I got two more alarms
to turn off when I get in.
I'll cut them. You stabbed me
in the motherfucking leg.
I'll put this
in your fucking ribs, trust me.
Come on, get to it.
[keypad beeping]
-[error beep]
-Fuck!
Give me a sec.
I just gotta concentrate, okay?
[Dawson] Get to it. Come on.
[keypad beeping]
[error beep]
Nothing's happening.
I'm gonna fucking shoot him.
[keypad beeping]
What the fuck is that? Hey!
[suspenseful music playing]
[Ash grunts]
[Dawson whistles]
[suspenseful music continues]
[Ryan groans]
[groans]
[dramatic music playing]
-I need a gun.
-Don't kill him.
We need the code.
[dramatic music continues]
[gunshots]
-[car horn honks]
-[tires screeching]
[groaning]
[gunshot]
He's crossing the tracks. Go!
[dramatic music continues]
[music turns suspenseful]
[grunts]
He's over here!
Stay with him. Hold him!
[music turns dramatic]
[gunshot]
Give me the code,
and I'll let you go.
I'll do it.
[music stops]
Do it.
[sirens wailing]
No.
[somber music playing]
[officer 1] Put your hands up!
Hands where I can see them.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[somber music continues]
[officer 2]
Okay, stay right there.
Stay calm. Stay calm.
[officers shouting indistinctly]
[officer 1]
Let me see your hands!
-Easy, okay?
-Shut up!
Come on. In the car. Come on.
What is this?
I got documents that show
Optimo Pharmaceutical's products
have adverse effects,
and they knew about it.
They tried to cover up
the evidence.
I got the internal memos.
I got the e-mails.
I got everything.
Why do you have it?
This is what I do. I help people
who find things like this.
Who see things maybe
they shouldn't have,
who should have looked
the other way, but they can't.
Now I gotta turn it over
to somebody I trust.
Yeah.
[somber music continues]
[music fades out]
It's a little heavy there.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
[soft dramatic music playing]
[bell ringing]
[blows whistle]
[ominous music playing]
[inaudible dialogue]
[train horn blaring]
[Karen Marks's "Cold Café"
playing]
♪ On the esplanade ♪
♪ My coffee's gone cold ♪
♪ I won't forget the sounds ♪
♪ You left me ♪
♪ Love and television ♪
♪ Don't give it a name ♪
♪ Take it anyway ♪
♪ There's no shelter
In my life ♪
♪ Your eyes in mine ♪
♪ Smoke in our mouths
Till morning ♪
♪ Your words in my head ♪
♪ I don't sleep anymore ♪
♪ On the esplanade ♪
♪ My coffee's gone cold ♪
♪ I won't forget the sounds ♪
♪ You left me ♪
♪ On the esplanade ♪
♪ My coffee's gone cold ♪
♪ I won't forget the sounds ♪
♪ You left me ♪
♪ I don't sleep ♪
♪ I don't sleep anymore ♪
♪ Anymore ♪
[song fades out]
[dramatic music playing]
[music ends]